NAKUL DESHMUKH

Vinkar Colony, Manewada, Nagpur, Maharashtra – 440027 email-nakuldeshmukh619@gmail.com

Mobile No. 9028838663 Linkedin - @nakuldex

SUMMARY

Veteran and L3 certified Python Developer with 5+ years of relevant experience. Automated 300+ variety of manual processes. Working independently and leading a small team. Strong in analytical, technical and automation opportunity hunting skills. Delivered plenty of End-to-end and easy to maintain automated process solutions. Currently serving as Tech lead.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Organization: Wipro Technologies

Account: Intel

30/03/2017 to Present day Pune (Remote), India 01/04/2021 to Present Day WFH

- Contributing to Open-source Linux OS project by Automating tests. (Linux Testing program).
- Learned new Automation Techniques, Frameworks, and security.
- Gained expertise in Selenium, PyTest, Pandas, Linux CLI, API building.
- Hands on experience on deploying and managing applications on AWS.
- Experience of CICD pipeline building maintaining.
- Hard earned expertise in clear Logic building, problem solving and critical thinking.
- Delivered Automation as a Service project (AaaS) i.e., an end-to-end Test automation framework with 400+ Test cases hosted on CICD platform. AaaS includes webpage automation using Page-object model, improved XPATHs definitions and Selenium, CLI automations using Paramiko, & API triggers/Microservices using Flask.
- Worked with teams across locations for Power BI automation. Independently created Python Glue scripts
 that reconcile data from different sources into one for Power BI tool. Quickly learned Pandas, RE and
 MySQL for this work.

Account: Chemours 30/03/2017 to 31/03/2021
Pune/WFH, India

- Learned business communication skill, interacted with clients across the world, made good professional relations
- Started working on Automation challenges with this project. Developed scripts for Automated infra
 monitoring, DB access management, SAP ticket/ID creation, User access management. Enabled teams to
 achieve SLA targets by building live Dashboard and Saved 1300+ manual hours. Participated in 'Botathon
 2021' for Automation Anywhere skills.
- Learned to troubleshoot and maintain legacy automation scripts. Analysis of Reports.
- Contributed to NPT v10 development by working on backend using Java 8 skill.
- Helped HR team by building easy to use Resume parser based on ML model.

SKILLS

Python, Java 8, DSA	Automation Anywhere,	Git, Jira,	CICD, Microservices,
Selenium, XPaths, Sikuli,	Linux, Windows, AWS	Pytest, Pandas, Flask	SQL, Logic building

EDUCATION

M. Tech (Work integrated) in IT with 8.2 CGPA.

B. Sc in Statistics with 7.0 CGPA

INTRESTS AND HOBBIES

 Like to play guitar and keyboard. Tutor for Statistics, Coding.

Following technical trends and ROBO science topics.